<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Introducing Luppoleto Brewing Company</title>
    <link>http://www.luppoleto.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Introducing Luppoleto Brewing Company</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://www.luppoleto.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>The Crowd At the Gates</title>
      <link>http://www.luppoleto.com/posts/gateway-beer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.luppoleto.com/posts/gateway-beer/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Craft brewers who make a &lt;em&gt;Bud Light Alternative&lt;/em&gt; as a gateway for macro-beer drinkers may get stuck brewing that &amp;ldquo;boring&amp;rdquo; beer forever and not actually getting anyone past the gate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the beer industry grows in leaps and bounds, new customers come from one of these three groups:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wine + Spirit Drinkers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Macro Beer Drinkers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;New Drinkers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since it is by far the largest group, the wisest strategy aims to convert Macro Beer Drinkers to Craft. First, they already drink beer. Sure, they prefer the neutral stuff but with the right stepping stone they may find their way into the fold, right? Then again, swapping mass market swill for a small-scale version of the &lt;em&gt;same thing&lt;/em&gt; is simple slight of hand; it doesn&amp;rsquo;t move the drinker meaningfully closer to craft. It&amp;rsquo;s like trading one set of training wheels for another&amp;hellip;more expensive, hand-crafted set. They&amp;rsquo;re no closer to riding properly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What we want is to take away one of the training wheels; make them a little unsteady but provide some support. If the gateway beer takes no convincing, it isn&amp;rsquo;t a gateway at all. In the same way you know you&amp;rsquo;ve underbid the project when you get a quick and enthusiastic &amp;ldquo;Deal!&amp;rdquo; in reply. There should be contemplation. They must be unsure about those first few sips. Some will retreat to the comfort of 2 extra wheels. Others, emboldened by their success, will ditch the training wheels altogether.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Or at least that is our theory. So no, there will not be a &lt;em&gt;Bud Light Alternative&lt;/em&gt; on the menu. Budwieser, Miller, Coors and Corona have the light lager area pretty well covered. They make an excellent, clean, refreshing example of the style. But if you are looking for more or even just a little curious, come see us.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Luppoleto Brewing Company</title>
      <link>http://www.luppoleto.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2016 00:24:27 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.luppoleto.com/about/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h3 id=&#34;our-team&#34;&gt;Our Team&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;James Wright&amp;hellip;.and a secret group of advisors, clandestinely scheming to take over the world; one beer at a time. Wondering all the while, if that is really how you spell &amp;ldquo;scheming&amp;rdquo;&amp;hellip;it looks weird, right?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;our-location&#34;&gt;Our Location&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By the airport&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-full-story-behind-the-name-luppoleto&#34;&gt;The Full Story Behind the Name: Luppoleto&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Luppoleto means hop farm or hopyard in Italian. It pays homage to the Italian heritage on my mother’s side and agricultural heritage on my father’s side&amp;hellip;and the craziness I inherited from both sides that led me to plant 60 hop plants nearly ten years ago and set in motion a series of events that led to opening a brewery!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;the-italian-bit&#34;&gt;The Italian bit….&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He even looked American. At least to her. Blond hair and blue eyes were a rarity in their tiny Italian village and she took notice. He was building a new life in America and had returned to his childhood village to find a bride. She lept at the opportunity. Three generations later, blond hair and blue eyes only further obscure my quarter-Italian heritage. The majority is Irish &amp;amp; English at this point but I still feel a deeper connection to that tiny Italian village. Perhaps it&amp;rsquo;s because I knew my Italian great-grandparents and heard their immigration story first hand. Or maybe it&amp;rsquo;s because I had the privilege of visiting that Italian village and meeting my relatives, many of whom still live in the same homes as they did when Noni &amp;amp; Papi left.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Although I didn’t fully digest it at age 16, I have come to appreciate my visit to Italy as one of the most impactful experiences of my life. When I decided to open my own place, I wanted to pay homage to my Italian heritage. Noni was one the most welcoming, caring and generous people I&amp;rsquo;ve ever met. And nearly all of my Italian cousins extended the same hospitality during our visit. Beer may not be as celebrated there but my great-grandparents who left behind the terraced vineyards for those amber waves of grain – they paved the way for this opportunity and so I honor that with the Italian name for Hop farm: Luppoleto and I hope to honor their memory by showing the same gracious hospitality they always demonstrated.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;the-farming-bit&#34;&gt;The farming bit…&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My grandfather on the other side was a farmer. I only knew him as a salesman because it had grown difficult to &lt;em&gt;make a living on the farm&lt;/em&gt; but they lived on the family farm; or the few remaining acres along &lt;strong&gt;Wright Street&lt;/strong&gt;. The road was named for the farm and the farmers (my grandfather and great grandfather) who dug it with axes, horses and ploughs. While there were no longer animals or barns, the homestead and an ample vegetable garden offered evidence of their agricultural past.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My dad adopted his father’s love of growing vegetables and he passed that along to me. I even got a job working on a farm for a couple years before I realized just how grueling it is and how comfortable (and air conditioned) software development can be. Years later, like many of us immersed in a digital world of bits, I craved a connection to something real, something physical. This is what drew me to homebrewing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is something special about making a product that can be physically shared and enjoyed but, like gardening, the process is governed by natural laws. You prepare the environment for something to grow and then you are bound by its timeline. In the world of instant gratification this is a valuable zen-like practice. You can’t make it go faster without changing the outcome. Like fruits and vegetables, there was a natural cadence to the process, a natural ripening. It was not long before I decided to fully embrace my agricultural past and grow my own hops.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Growing hops may not seem noteworthy. Plenty of homebrewers plant a hop plant or two in their yard but I am not a normal homebrewer. I planted 60. We erected a trellis system – which the hops promptly outgrew, then built a new, larger system with 18 foot poles and aircraft cable. We put in untold hours weeding, picking and maintaining those hops. It turns out I am &lt;em&gt;still&lt;/em&gt; not a farmer but I need to learn that lesson the hard way every few years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I only needed a small dose of agriculture – a hop garden would have been sufficient. But this crazy idea wasn’t without its perks. The Wright Nano Hopyard didn’t lead to a side business or the cheap endless supply of brewing ingredients I had imagined but it did earn me a trip to Sierra Nevada Beer Camp, an experience which cemented my future in the beer business.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The land where the Wright Nano Hopyard was born is up for sale so I moved some of the surviving plants to my father’s garden. The rest will come live here.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hopigarchy IPA</title>
      <link>http://www.luppoleto.com/beers/hopigarchy-ipa/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2016 00:24:27 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.luppoleto.com/beers/hopigarchy-ipa/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Alas, we must yield to the unrelenting rule of hops. Hop-forward beers catalyzed the craft beer revolution in the good ol&amp;rsquo; US of A. Modedration does not live here. Citrusy, piney &amp;amp; resiney hops greet your nose followed by loads of hop flavor. Bready malt &amp;amp; wheat offer temporary repreive before a nice smack of pity bitterness on the finish.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hours &amp; Directions</title>
      <link>http://www.luppoleto.com/hours-directions/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2016 00:24:27 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.luppoleto.com/hours-directions/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h3 id=&#34;taproom-hours&#34;&gt;Taproom Hours&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The tasting room will be open for pints&amp;hellip;someday soon:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mon: CLOSED&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tue: 4-8pm&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wed: 4-8pm&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Thu: 4-8pm&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fri: 4-10pm&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sat: Noon-10pm&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sun: CLOSED&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;growler-fills&#34;&gt;Growler Fills&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A brewery without beer is like breakfast without OJ (and you know what happened to him). We do not currently fill growlers because our system is quite small and we haven&amp;rsquo;t been open long enough to know if offering growlers will negatively impact the variety available on tap in the tasting room. In other words. We will grow into it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;outside-food&#34;&gt;Outside Food&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is like giving people instructions as to how to leave a message on your answering machine. Wait &amp;ldquo;answering maching&amp;rdquo;? Sigh&amp;hellip;.I&amp;rsquo;m old. Voicemail. Argh, everyone just TXTs these days. This is a terrible analogy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyhow, YES you can bring outside food. Or you can order from any of the restaurants that offer takeout nearby. We don&amp;rsquo;t have any of our own food&amp;hellip;yet.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Just What We Need...Another Brewery</title>
      <link>http://www.luppoleto.com/posts/another-brewery/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2016 00:24:27 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.luppoleto.com/posts/another-brewery/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Yes, another brewery will be opening soon. And it won&amp;rsquo;t be the last. I know what you&amp;rsquo;re thinking: why? There are already 4000+ do we really need as many breweries are there are Starbucks?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;‎Do not seek to follow in the footsteps of others, instead, seek what they sought.&amp;rdquo; - Matsuo Basho&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then again&amp;hellip;nearly everyone who missed an opportunity was thinking, &amp;ldquo;Do we really need another X?&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fill in the blank:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Burger Place&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Pizza Joint&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dollar Store!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You name it &amp;ndash; the market was, by all appearces completely tied up and humming along. When all the sudden 5 Guys comes along and says, &amp;ldquo;We don&amp;rsquo;t care about McDonald&amp;rsquo;s, Burger King &amp;amp; Hardee&amp;rsquo;s we think there is room for another player.&amp;rdquo; Yet, there was an opportunity because the established players let down their guard.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Like the fast food giants; Budweiser, Miller &amp;amp; Coors got complacent. Craft breweries stepped up to deliver local, unique &amp;amp; flavorful options and filled a gap in the marketplace that only a few enterprising pioneers like Ken Grossman &amp;amp; Fritz Maytag had identified. But even Mr. Grossman never expected the boom we have today.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And I think there will be a handful of big regional powerhouses. While thousands of ultra local, nano-breweries fill in the gaps.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So we strive not to be just another: &amp;ldquo;me too&amp;rdquo; brewery. We want to be part of the local community. We want to be the best local beer joint. We want to be an attraction for visitors. We aim to be small.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Maybe say something about the stones, the sand and water analogy.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stouty McStoutface</title>
      <link>http://www.luppoleto.com/beers/stouty-mcstoutface/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2016 00:24:27 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.luppoleto.com/beers/stouty-mcstoutface/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Ahh the beloved research vessel whose name rose so clearly to the top like the creamy
foam atop this beer.Is this a shameless attempt to profit of a popular meme? Maybe.
But who could stay mad at that face?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Well isn&amp;rsquo;t that just blacker than the ace of spades!&amp;rdquo;
- My Neighbor, Peering into the homebrew kettle&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;See what we did here was make a nice English Style Export Stout (a bit sweeter than its
continental cousin) and added a bunch of cold-brewed coffee &amp;ndash; think chocolate covered espresso beans.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yeah. It&amp;rsquo;s prettty good.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>