<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Luppoleto Brewing Company</title>
    <link>http://www.luppoleto.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Luppoleto Brewing Company</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2016 00:24:27 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://www.luppoleto.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>About Luppoleto Brewing Company</title>
      <link>http://www.luppoleto.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2016 00:24:27 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.luppoleto.com/about/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h3 id=&#34;our-team&#34;&gt;Our Team&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;James Wright&amp;hellip;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;our-location&#34;&gt;Our Location&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By the airport&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hours &amp; Directions</title>
      <link>http://www.luppoleto.com/hours-directions/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2016 00:24:27 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.luppoleto.com/hours-directions/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h3 id=&#34;taproom-hours&#34;&gt;Taproom Hours&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The tasting room is open for pints:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mon: CLOSED&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tue: 4-8pm&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wed: 4-8pm&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Thu: 4-8pm&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fri: 4-10pm&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sat: Noon-10pm&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sun: CLOSED&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;growler-fills&#34;&gt;Growler Fills&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A brewery without beer is like breakfast without OJ (and you know what happened to him). We do not currently fill growlers because our system is quite small and we haven&amp;rsquo;t been open long enough to know if offering growlers will negatively impact the variety available on tap in the tasting room. In other words. We will grow into it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;outside-food&#34;&gt;Outside Food&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is like giving people instructions as to how to leave a message on your answering machine. Wait &amp;ldquo;answering maching&amp;rdquo;? Sigh&amp;hellip;.I&amp;rsquo;m old. Voicemail.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyhow, YES you can bring outside food. Or you can order from any of the restaurants that offer takeout nearby. We don&amp;rsquo;t have any of our own food.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Just What We Need...Another Brewery</title>
      <link>http://www.luppoleto.com/posts/another-brewery/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2016 00:24:27 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.luppoleto.com/posts/another-brewery/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;‎Do not seek to follow in the footsteps of others, instead, seek what they sought.&amp;rdquo; - Matsuo Basho&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yes, another brewery will be opening soon. And it won&amp;rsquo;t be the last. I know what you&amp;rsquo;re thinking: why? There are already 4000+ do we really need as many breweries are there are Starbucks?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then again&amp;hellip;nearly everyone who missed an opportunity was thinking, &amp;ldquo;Do we really need another X?&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fill in the blank:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Burger Place&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Pizza Joint&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dollar Store!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You name it &amp;ndash; the market was, by all appearces completely tied up and humming along. When all the sudden 5 Guys comes along and says, &amp;ldquo;We don&amp;rsquo;t care about McDonald&amp;rsquo;s, Burger King &amp;amp; Hardee&amp;rsquo;s we think there is room for another player.&amp;rdquo; Yet, there was an opportunity because the established players let down their guard.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Like the fast food giants; Budweiser, Miller &amp;amp; Coors got complacent. Craft breweries stepped up to deliver local, unique &amp;amp; flavorful options and filled a gap in the marketplace that only a few enterprising pioneers like Ken Grossman &amp;amp; Fritz Maytag had identified. But even Mr. Grossman never expected the boom we have today.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And I think there will be a handful of big regional powerhouses. While thousands of ultra local, nano-breweries fill in the gaps.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So we strive not to be just another: &amp;ldquo;me too&amp;rdquo; brewery. We want to be part of the local community. We want to be the best local beer joint. We want to be an attraction for visitors. We aim to be small.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Maybe say something about the stones, the sand and water analogy.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stouty McStoutface</title>
      <link>http://www.luppoleto.com/beers/stouty-mcstoutface/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2016 00:24:27 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.luppoleto.com/beers/stouty-mcstoutface/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Ahh the beloved research vessel whose name rose so clearly to the top like the creamy
foam atop this beer.Is this a shameless attempt to profit of a popular meme? Maybe.
But who could stay mad at that face?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Well isn&amp;rsquo;t that just blacker than the ace of spades!&amp;rdquo;
- My Neighbor, Peering into the homebrew kettle&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;See what we did here was make a nice English Style Export Stout (a bit sweeter than its
continental cousin) and added a bunch of cold-brewed coffee &amp;ndash; think chocolate covered espresso beans.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yeah. It&amp;rsquo;s prettty good.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>