<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Introducing Luppoleto Brewing Company</title>
    <link>http://www.luppoleto.com/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Introducing Luppoleto Brewing Company</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://www.luppoleto.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Windsor Locks Adopts New Brewing Regulations!</title>
      <link>http://www.luppoleto.com/posts/new-regulations-adopted/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.luppoleto.com/posts/new-regulations-adopted/</guid>
      <description>&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;ldquo;With the brewery in place, I still had one small obstacle to clear before I could open the pub: My plan to open a brewery in in Delaware was totally illegal.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;– Sam Calagione, &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.dogfish.com/&#34;&gt;Founder Dogfish Head Craft Brewery&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In 1995, Sam co-authored a bill and presented it on the floor of the Delaware State Senate. We merely worked with the Town of Windsor Locks to bring their zoning regulations into parity with the updated &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cga.ct.gov/2012/ACT/PA/2012PA-00017-R00HB-05021-PA.htm&#34;&gt;Connecticut State statutes&lt;/a&gt;. Despite the fact our regulatory hurdle was much, much smaller, I feel a sense of kinship over this small bit of shared history.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bottom line: we helped change the regulations to pave the way for our Rt. 75 Taproom.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Next: We must apply for a permit under these new regulations. A sign will be posted at our proposed location and notice will be published in the local paper in advance of the public hearing. I suspect if there is any resistance to this project, that’s when it will emerge. We will be sure to let everyone know the dates so we can get a good turnout in support.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;For those of you who took the time to come out to Town Hall last night, THANK YOU! We truly appreciate your support and enthusiasm.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cheers!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;JW&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Crowd At the Gates</title>
      <link>http://www.luppoleto.com/posts/gateway-beer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.luppoleto.com/posts/gateway-beer/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Craft brewers who make a &lt;em&gt;Bud Light Alternative&lt;/em&gt; as a gateway for macro-beer drinkers may get stuck brewing that &amp;ldquo;boring&amp;rdquo; beer forever and not actually getting anyone past the gate.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the beer industry grows in leaps and bounds, new customers come from one of these three groups:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wine + Spirit Drinkers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Macro Beer Drinkers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;New Drinkers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since it is by far the largest group, the wisest strategy aims to convert Macro Beer Drinkers to Craft. First, they already drink beer. Sure, they prefer the neutral stuff but with the right stepping stone they may find their way into the fold, right? Then again, swapping mass market swill for a small-scale version of the &lt;em&gt;same thing&lt;/em&gt; is simple slight of hand; it doesn&amp;rsquo;t move the drinker meaningfully closer to craft. It&amp;rsquo;s like trading one set of training wheels for another&amp;hellip;more expensive, hand-crafted set. They&amp;rsquo;re no closer to riding properly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What we want is to take away one of the training wheels; make them a little unsteady but provide some support. If the gateway beer takes no convincing, it isn&amp;rsquo;t a gateway at all. In the same way you know you&amp;rsquo;ve underbid the project when you get a quick and enthusiastic &amp;ldquo;Deal!&amp;rdquo; in reply. There should be contemplation. They must be unsure about those first few sips. Some will retreat to the comfort of 2 extra wheels. Others, emboldened by their success, will ditch the training wheels altogether.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Or at least that is our theory. So no, there will not be a &lt;em&gt;Bud Light Alternative&lt;/em&gt; on the menu. Budwieser, Miller, Coors and Corona have the light lager area pretty well covered. They make an excellent, clean, refreshing example of the style. But if you are looking for more or even just a little curious, come see us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cheers!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;JW&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How I Got To Brew at Sierra Nevada</title>
      <link>http://www.luppoleto.com/posts/beer-camp/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.luppoleto.com/posts/beer-camp/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;In the Summer of 2011, I had the amazing opportunity to attend Beer Camp at the &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.sierranevada.com/&#34;&gt;Sierra Nevada Brewery&lt;/a&gt; in Chico, California. Beer Camp was created as a way to share the Sierra Nevada story with some of the brewery&amp;rsquo;s biggest accounts and distributors. A few years ago, they opened it up to the beer loving public. Regular folks, like me (I use the term &amp;ldquo;regular&amp;rdquo; loosely) could compete for a chance to get the same VIP tour and brew a batch on the pilot system. All you had to do was tell them why you deserve to go to Beer Camp&amp;hellip;in a video.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;our-beer-raiders-of-the-last-hops&#34;&gt;Our Beer: Raiders of the Last Hops&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The winners of the National Beer Camp Contest collaborated to create a unique recipe which we had the distinct privilege of brewing on the pilot system at the Sierra Nevada Brewery in Chico, California. Once we found out that our beer would be released around Christmas time we wanted to make it reasonably high in alcohol (for that nice warming effect) but not just another spiced beer. So instead we decided to go with an Imperial Red Ale. The Red Ale style is usually very accesible with its big malty body but we decided to take it up a notch or 3.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sierra Nevada has been growing a few acres of their own organic hops on premises and we were able to harvest the last row for our beer; hence the name &amp;ldquo;Raiders of the LAST Hops&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Most hops are kiln-dryed prior to use but we put our hops in &amp;ldquo;wet&amp;rdquo;, fresh from the field. This gives a distinct floral/grassy character to the beer which is only available around hop harvest time. Finally, we decided it would be interesting to introduce a subtle hint of wood character by aging (briefly) on Citrus wood. This will not be a strong, oakey, smack you in the face like a Napa cab wood character but just a nuance. And to top it all off: we added a bit of Nelson Sauvin - a bombastically fruity hop - along with the wood&amp;hellip;because we could! Again it will be a background note because this beer is all about the estate grown hops.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So without further ado, here&amp;rsquo;s my winning entry (Fair warning: it&amp;rsquo;s really goofy &amp;amp; quite long)&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&#34;640&#34; height=&#34;360&#34; src=&#34;http://www.youtube.com/embed/PHFa-hgHPDo&#34; frameborder=&#34;0&#34; allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I returned with a contagious excitement and word of my adventure found its way to the local news:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&#34;640&#34; height=&#34;360&#34; src=&#34;http://www.youtube.com/embed/30pS7twTHQw&#34; frameborder=&#34;0&#34; allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;raiders-of-the-last-hops-comes-to-connecticut&#34;&gt;Raiders of the Last Hops Comes to Connecticut!&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To promote the beer I tapped into my inner-designer and whipped up these posters. A framed version still hangs proudly in my office.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://farm9.staticflickr.com/8230/8380414769_96f35a0f7a_c.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Raiders of the Last Hops Poster&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Plan B Burger Bar graciously hosted tapping events in 2012 at 3 of their Connecticut locations:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Plan B: Glastonbury 120 Hebron Avenue, Glastonbury, CT 06033&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Plan B: West Hartford 138 Park Road, West Hartford, CT 06119&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Plan B: Simsbury 4 Railroad Street, Simsbury, CT 06070&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even if you missed the events you can always count on Plan B to have a great taplist and delicious food (I strongly recommend the Blue Chips).&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Just What We Need...Another Brewery</title>
      <link>http://www.luppoleto.com/posts/another-brewery/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2016 00:24:27 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.luppoleto.com/posts/another-brewery/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;‎Do not seek to follow in the footsteps of others, instead, seek what they sought.&amp;rdquo; - Matsuo Basho&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then again&amp;hellip;nearly everyone who missed an opportunity was thinking, &amp;ldquo;Do we really need another X?&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fill in the blank:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Burger Place&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Pizza Joint&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dollar Store!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You name it &amp;ndash; the market was, by all appearces completely tied up and humming along. When all the sudden 5 Guys comes along and says, &amp;ldquo;We don&amp;rsquo;t care about McDonald&amp;rsquo;s, Burger King &amp;amp; Hardee&amp;rsquo;s we think there is room for another player.&amp;rdquo; Yet, there was an opportunity because the established players let down their guard.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Like the fast food giants; Budweiser, Miller &amp;amp; Coors got complacent. Craft breweries stepped up to deliver local, unique &amp;amp; flavorful options and filled a gap in the marketplace that only a few enterprising pioneers like Ken Grossman &amp;amp; Fritz Maytag had identified. But even Mr. Grossman never expected the boom we have today.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And I think there will be a handful of big regional powerhouses. While thousands of ultra local, nano-breweries fill in the gaps.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So we strive not to be just another: &amp;ldquo;me too&amp;rdquo; brewery. We want to be part of the local community. We want to be the best local beer joint. We want to be an attraction for visitors. We aim to be small.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Maybe say something about the stones, the sand and water analogy.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>