<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Introducing Luppoleto Brewing Company</title>
    <link>http://www.luppoleto.com/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Introducing Luppoleto Brewing Company</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://www.luppoleto.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>The Crowd At the Gates</title>
      <link>http://www.luppoleto.com/posts/gateway-beer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.luppoleto.com/posts/gateway-beer/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Craft brewers who make a &lt;em&gt;Bud Light Alternative&lt;/em&gt; as a gateway for macro-beer drinkers may get stuck brewing that &amp;ldquo;boring&amp;rdquo; beer forever and not actually getting anyone past the gate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the beer industry grows in leaps and bounds, new customers come from one of these three groups:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wine + Spirit Drinkers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Macro Beer Drinkers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;New Drinkers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since it is by far the largest group, the wisest strategy aims to convert Macro Beer Drinkers to Craft. First, they already drink beer. Sure, they prefer the neutral stuff but with the right stepping stone they may find their way into the fold, right? Then again, swapping mass market swill for a small-scale version of the &lt;em&gt;same thing&lt;/em&gt; is simple slight of hand; it doesn&amp;rsquo;t move the drinker meaningfully closer to craft. It&amp;rsquo;s like trading one set of training wheels for another&amp;hellip;more expensive, hand-crafted set. They&amp;rsquo;re no closer to riding properly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What we want is to take away one of the training wheels; make them a little unsteady but provide some support. If the gateway beer takes no convincing, it isn&amp;rsquo;t a gateway at all. In the same way you know you&amp;rsquo;ve underbid the project when you get a quick and enthusiastic &amp;ldquo;Deal!&amp;rdquo; in reply. There should be contemplation. They must be unsure about those first few sips. Some will retreat to the comfort of 2 extra wheels. Others, emboldened by their success, will ditch the training wheels altogether.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Or at least that is our theory. So no, there will not be a &lt;em&gt;Bud Light Alternative&lt;/em&gt; on the menu. Budwieser, Miller, Coors and Corona have the light lager area pretty well covered. They make an excellent, clean, refreshing example of the style. But if you are looking for more or even just a little curious, come see us.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Just What We Need...Another Brewery</title>
      <link>http://www.luppoleto.com/posts/another-brewery/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2016 00:24:27 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.luppoleto.com/posts/another-brewery/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Yes, another brewery will be opening soon. And it won&amp;rsquo;t be the last. I know what you&amp;rsquo;re thinking: why? There are already 4000+ do we really need as many breweries are there are Starbucks?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;‎Do not seek to follow in the footsteps of others, instead, seek what they sought.&amp;rdquo; - Matsuo Basho&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then again&amp;hellip;nearly everyone who missed an opportunity was thinking, &amp;ldquo;Do we really need another X?&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fill in the blank:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Burger Place&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Pizza Joint&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dollar Store!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You name it &amp;ndash; the market was, by all appearces completely tied up and humming along. When all the sudden 5 Guys comes along and says, &amp;ldquo;We don&amp;rsquo;t care about McDonald&amp;rsquo;s, Burger King &amp;amp; Hardee&amp;rsquo;s we think there is room for another player.&amp;rdquo; Yet, there was an opportunity because the established players let down their guard.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Like the fast food giants; Budweiser, Miller &amp;amp; Coors got complacent. Craft breweries stepped up to deliver local, unique &amp;amp; flavorful options and filled a gap in the marketplace that only a few enterprising pioneers like Ken Grossman &amp;amp; Fritz Maytag had identified. But even Mr. Grossman never expected the boom we have today.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And I think there will be a handful of big regional powerhouses. While thousands of ultra local, nano-breweries fill in the gaps.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So we strive not to be just another: &amp;ldquo;me too&amp;rdquo; brewery. We want to be part of the local community. We want to be the best local beer joint. We want to be an attraction for visitors. We aim to be small.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Maybe say something about the stones, the sand and water analogy.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>